we're gonna speak about some varieties
我们要谈一些品种
of auctions to get a sense for the
拍卖以了解
richness of the space because we often
空间的丰富性，因为我们经常
think about auctions about something as
考虑拍卖有关
something very specific but in fact
很具体但实际上
auctions are very broad an option is any
拍卖的范围很广
mechanism that allocates resources
资源分配机制
typically scarce resources among agents
代理商之间通常稀缺的资源
who have their own interests and we know
他们有自己的利益，我们知道
of many examples the governed sale of
在许多例子中，
whether the electric mech
是否电动
electromagnetic spectrum or mineral
电磁频谱或矿物
rights drilling rights for oil
石油开采权
what-have-you privatization of national
你对国民有什么私有化
assets those are all typically put to
这些资产通常都放在
bid in one way another stock markets are
以另一种方式出价
very famous to cited auction where there
非常有名的引用拍卖那里
are many buyers and sellers rfqs or
有很多买卖双方的rfqs或
requests for quotes are a standard
报价请求是标准
mechanism for a company or a government
公司或政府的机制
to solicit offers to supply them with
征求报价以向他们提供
goods or services at the most attractive
最具吸引力的商品或服务
terms these are called reverse auctions
这些术语称为反向拍卖
we already mentioned the FCC spectrum
我们已经提到了FCC频谱
auction by way of sale of national
通过国民拍卖的方式进行拍卖
resources real estate a sales are often
资源房地产销售经常
conducted on some kind of tender a bid
以某种形式进行招标
basis where multiple people offer make
多人提供的基础
offers and according to certain rules
报价并根据某些规则
and certainly consumer based reactions
当然还有基于消费者的反应
such as the ones conducted on eBay a
例如在eBay上进行的
very famous where everything from cars
非常有名的地方，一切都来自汽车
to to old CDs are are sold there are
到旧CD出售有
many other examples and we should bear
许多其他例子，我们应该承担
in mind that often the goods being sold
请记住，经常出售商品
or are not necessarily the standard once
或不一定是标准
you think of in options as a computer
您认为选项就像一台电脑
scientist I should point out many
科学家，我应该指出很多
applications of auction in competing
拍卖在竞争中的应用
environments so for example
环境，例如
firk bandwidth is a scarce resource and
发射带宽是一种稀缺资源，
there is an opportunity to auction off
有机会拍卖
the right to use bandwidth to highest
最高使用带宽的权利
bidders in advertising options famously
广告选择竞标者
on Google and other advertising
在Google和其他广告上
platforms advertisers bid for the right
平台广告商竞标权利
to present us with certain offers when
向我们提供某些优惠
you search for certain keywords or even
您搜索某些关键字，甚至
when we just browse certain web pages
当我们只浏览某些网页时
there are display advertising and they
有展示广告，他们
too are open for for a bid there are
也有公开招标
peer-to-peer networks and many other
对等网络和许多其他
applications in the computing
计算中的应用
environment so what are the kind of
环境，那是什么样的
auctions we see in fact the space of
拍卖实际上我们看到的空间
auctions is infinite here are some
拍卖是无限的，这里有一些
examples that begin to illustrate the
例子开始说明
richness of the space so we'll go over
空间的丰富性，我们将结束
those in in in order the English auction
那些以顺序进行的英语拍卖
the Japanese the Dutch the first price
日本人荷兰人第一价
sealed bid auction and the second price
密封投标拍卖和第二价格
sealed bid auction and finally the all
密封拍卖，最后全部
pay auction so let's go over those in
支付拍卖，让我们看看那些
turn the English auction is probably the
打开英语拍卖可能是
most familiar format this is the sort of
最常见的格式是
thing that in art auction houses I
在艺术品拍卖行中的东西
mekansm use they're so clear starts with
mekansm使用它们是如此清晰，从
some initial price often called the
一些初始价格通常称为
reservation or the reserve price and
保留或底价和
bittering the auctions shot sending
痛苦的拍卖镜头发送
prices and at some point to stop
价格，并在某个时候停止
shouting the auctioneer may try to
大喊拍卖师可能会尝试
control them into sedition high prices
控制他们进入煽动高价
but at some point the nobody says
但在某个时候，没人说
anything at that point the option is
那时的任何选择
closed and the highest bidder wins the
关闭，最高出价者中标
good at that price the Japanese auction
以这样的价格，日本拍卖行
is a less common term but it's similar
是一个不太常用的术语，但类似
to the English auction in that it's an
参加英国拍卖会
open outcry auction and the price
公开竞价拍卖和价格
ascends except here is the auctioneer
上升，除了这里是拍卖师
that calls out the prices
喊出价格
whether explicitly or by some mechanism
无论是明确地还是通过某种机制
like a clock that just continuously
就像一个持续不断的时钟
Rises and I think of all the bidders as
上升，我认为所有投标者都是
being in to begin with there so standing
在那里开始如此站立
there and maybe the auction start is
在那里，也许拍卖开始是
zero dollars for a television and
电视机零美元，
everybody says I'm in and then the price
大家都说我进去了然后价钱
starts to rise slowly and at some point
开始缓慢上升，并在某个时刻
bidders decide the price is too high for
竞标者认为价格过高
them and they sit down they're out of
他们，他们坐下，他们走了
the auction and this is irrevocable once
拍卖，这是一次不可撤销的
they sit down they cannot stand back up
他们坐下来，他们不能站起来
and when you have only one bitter left
当你只剩下一个苦
standing they get the good at that at
站立时，他们擅长于
that price this is very similar to the
这个价格非常类似于
English auction it's a little easier to
英文拍卖更容易
analyze among other things because the
进行分析，因为
price does rise continuously and there
价格确实持续上涨，
you don't have what you call jump it
你没有你所谓的跳跃
where somebody certainly offers a price
肯定有人要价的地方
that's much higher than the current
远高于目前
price and and if you want to think about
价格，如果您想考虑
it in terms of a game representation you
就游戏表现而言，
can imagine that in the English auction
可以想象在英国拍卖中
at every point in the game you have many
在游戏的每个点上，您都有很多
branches corresponding to the different
对应于不同的分支
sort of increases or jump bids one could
可以提高或提高出价的一种方式
give whereas here the game evolves in a
给予，而游戏在这里发展
very you know in a single predictable
你知道一个单一的可预测的
way that is the auction that's often
这种方式通常是拍卖
called the Japanese auction and staying
叫日本拍卖行
on the international theme we have the
关于国际主题，我们有
doctor auction this is a more standard
医生拍卖这是更标准的
term and it's so called because this is
这个词之所以被称为是因为
in fact the mechanism but to this day is
实际上，直到今天的机制是
used in the Dutch flower market so how
用在荷兰花卉市场上
does the Dutch often work because this
荷兰人经常工作是因为
is a descending auction like in the
是像在
Japanese auction is the option ear that
日本拍卖是一种选择
calls out prices again whether
再次召集价格
explicitly or by a mechanism and in fact
明确地或通过某种机制，实际上
in the Dutch flower market it's a clock
在荷兰花卉市场上，它是一个时钟
that starts at that everybody can look
始于每个人都可以看
at the end starts at a high price and
最后以高价开始
gradually goes down
逐渐下降
at some point the bidder claims the the
在某些时候，投标人要求
the objects say the flower palette by
对象说出的调色板
shouting mine or as it's the case and
喊我的或者是这样
the Dutch flower market hitting a buzzer
荷兰花卉市场蜂鸣器
and when they get it they when they hit
当他们拿到时
it they get that good for that price so
他们以那个价格得到了那么好的，所以
you can think of it as a game of chicken
你可以把它当成鸡的游戏
obviously everybody would like to get
显然每个人都想得到
the good at the lowest possible price
以尽可能低的价格出售商品
but if they wait too long somebody could
但是如果他们等待太久，有人可以
beat them to the punch this is the Dutch
击败他们，这是荷兰人
auction
拍卖
moving on to sealed bid auctions we we
继续进行密封的竞标拍卖，我们
get off the international theme these
摆脱这些国际主题
are called sealed bid auctions because
之所以称为密封竞标拍卖，是因为
unlike the ones we discussed so far
不像我们到目前为止讨论的那样
there's no open house try but imagine
没有开放的房子尝试，但想像
that everybody writes a an offer a bid
大家写要约
on a piece of paper and seals it in an
在一张纸上并将其密封在
envelope and hands it the auctioneer and
信封并递给拍卖师，
the auctioneer opens the envelope at the
拍卖师在
same time and and then then decides what
同时，然后决定什么
the outcome of the auction is and here
拍卖的结果在这里
are two example of how this might happen
是两个例子说明如何发生
the most common auction is the first
最常见的拍卖是第一次
price auction or first price sealed bid
价格拍卖或第一价格密封投标
auction so in this case the auctioneer
拍卖，因此在这种情况下，拍卖师
fix the bidder with the highest price as
将出价最高的竞标者确定为
the winner and have them pay their price
获胜者并让他们付出代价
seems very straightforward and a very
看起来非常直接，非常
common mechanism second price auction is
共同机制第二价格拍卖是
almost the same it's again the highest
几乎一样，再次是最高的
person who bid who wins the auction but
竞标的人谁赢得了拍卖会，但
they don't pay what they wrote down they
他们不付写下来的钱
pay what the highest rejected bid or the
支付最高拒绝出价或
second highest bid is and you might
第二高的出价是
scratch your head for a moment to say
挠头说一句话
why would I want to do this for example
我为什么要这样做
if I want to maximize my revenue as a
如果我想最大化我的收入
seller surely I'd get less money if I
卖方如果我能肯定会少赚钱
did the second price but when you think
做了第二个价格，但是当你认为
about it the answer isn't so simple
关于它，答案不是那么简单
because by changing the rules the
因为通过更改规则
auction people would bid differently in
拍卖人在
fact there's a famous result called the
事实上，有一个著名的结果叫做
revenue equivalence theorem
收益等价定理
shows that under certain conditions many
表明在某些条件下
auction formats that look very different
看起来非常不同的拍卖形式
in particular the first and second price
特别是第一和第二价格
sealed bid auctions actually an
密封竞标拍卖实际上是
expectation fetch the same price here
期望在这里获得相同的价格
for variety it's a very different sort
种类繁多
of auction and it's the old pay auction
拍卖，这是旧的薪酬拍卖
and so you have a good for sale and oh
所以你有一个很好的销售哦
maybe the good is a maybe that good is a
也许好是一个
$20 bill now imagine that I auction off
20美元的钞票现在想象我在拍卖
this $20 bill and here are the rules if
这20美元的钞票，如果
you bid in the auction you can write
您在拍卖中出价可以写
down any amount you want and piece of
减少您想要的任何金额
paper and if you're the highest guy and
纸，如果你是最高的人，
at the highest guy will win the auction
最高的人将赢得拍卖
so if you write down $3 and if your
因此，如果您写下$ 3，
highest guy you'll get this $20 bill for
最高的人，你会得到这20美元的钞票
3 $3 if you lost you will still have to
3 $ 3如果您输了，您仍然必须
pay your bid right so that's why it's
正确支付您的出价，这就是为什么
called an all pay auction and now think
叫全薪拍卖，现在想
for a moment what would you bid in such
一会儿你会出价
an auction surely so tempting you want
拍卖肯定很诱人
to bid something would you bid at least
出价某物您至少会出价
$1 for the right to to win this $20 bill
1美元，可赢得20美元的钞票
what happens if this wasn't a sealed bid
如果这不是密封投标，会发生什么
auction but an ascending option and
拍卖，但选择权上升
people could bid $1 and then somebody
人们可以出价1美元，然后有人
could bid $2 how would you behave in
可以出价2美元，您的行为如何
this auction so we've seen several
这次拍卖，所以我们已经看到了几个
auction type now the English Japanese
拍卖类型现在为英文日文
the Dutch sealed bid auctions they all
荷兰人全部竞标
pay auction and this might suggests that
付费拍卖，这可能表明
to understand the space of auctions you
了解您的拍卖空间
should enumerate the different option
应该列举不同的选择
types and study them but in fact the
类型并研究它们，但实际上
space of auctions is infinite in an
拍卖的空间是无限的
option is simply a negotiation mechanism
选择只是一种协商机制
that is first market-based so that means
首先是基于市场的，这意味着
that there is some sort of rules that
有某种规则
govern it and typically involve
治理它，通常涉及
some sort of currency of the marketplace
某种市场货币
for example money it's mediated by a
例如金钱是由
central authority the auctioneer and it
中央拍卖行及其
has very well-defined rules that
有非常明确的规则
everybody goes by and everybody knows
每个人都经过，每个人都知道
that everybody goes by their common
每个人都遵循他们的共同点
knowledge and the three kind of rules
知识和三种规则
that we need to specify it in order to
我们需要指定它以便
specify an auction there are the bidding
指定一个拍卖会
rules there are the information rules
规则有信息规则
and are the market clearing rules and if
市场清算规则以及
you specify those you specify the
您指定那些您指定
auction so what we mean by bidding rules
拍卖，所以我们所说的竞标规则
we really mean who can bid when they bid
我们的意思是说谁可以出价
what they can bid and some restrictions
他们可以出价和一些限制
there are you know for example in an
你知道例如
ascendant we had bid auction I have to
上升，我们不得不进行拍卖
bid the current highest price in other
出价其他单位的当前最高价
auctions I have to bid my own price we
拍卖我必须出价自己的价格
may not allow people to bid arbitrarily
可能不允许人们任意竞标
high we will make with some budget
高，我们将用一些预算
constraints bids may have expiration
限制条件出价可能已到期
dates they may may be subject to
他们可能要遵守的日期
withdrawals or not and so on and so
是否提现等等
forth so these are all the bidding rules
就是这些，所有的竞标规则
very importantly are the information
非常重要的是信息
disclosure rules and for example in a
披露规则，例如
sealed bid auction we when I bid you
密封竞标拍卖，当我竞标时我们
don't see my bid but do you know that I
没有看到我的出价，但是你知道我吗
bid already that's a very important
出价已经非常重要
information from you do you know who are
来自您的信息，您知道谁是谁
the set of people who might be bidding
可能正在竞标的人
so information dissemination here is
所以这里的信息传播是
very critical to the market place and
对市场非常关键，
has to be explicitly specified and
必须明确指定
finally when all is said and done the
终于，当一切都说完了，
bidding is done based on information
根据信息进行投标
that agents do and don't have you need
代理商需要和不需要的
to clear the market and market clearing
清理市场和市场清理
rules are also multifaceted there's a
规则也是多方面的
questions of when to clear for example
例如何时清除的问题
you might clear the market
你可能会清理市场
many times if you have multiple Goods
如果您有多个商品很多次
you may clear the market once and
您可能会清除市场一次，
certain set of goods will be sold and
某些商品将被出售，
clear again and another set and so on
再次清除和另一组，依此类推
you might for example decide when to
例如，您可能决定何时
clear based on activities and so in some
根据活动明确，因此在某些情况下
of the online auctions you will see that
在网上拍卖中，您会看到
the auction ends at noon or after a
拍卖在中午或
periods of 10 minutes of inactivity that
闲置10分钟
is 10 minutes during which nobody place
10分钟内没有人放置
any bid whichever is later it's a very
任何出价，以较晚者为准
interesting market clearing rule so
有趣的市场清算规则
that's the - regarding the timing then
那是-关于时间
the allocation and the payment in other
分配和其他付款
words you've cleared the marketing to
您已清除行销的字词
say who got what who got for example in
说出谁得到了谁，例如
case of a single good who got the van
一辆面包车的单一商品的情况
Gogh and who pays what as we've seen may
梵高和谁支付我们所看到的可能
not only be the person of one who pays
不仅是付钱的人
for example in on all pay auction
例如在所有薪酬拍卖中
everybody who bid phase once we
每个竞标阶段的人
specified all of that we specify the
指定了所有我们指定的
auction and return
拍卖和退货